goldmic.com 2009-10-03

# Goldmic: The Hip-Hop Network: Privacy Policy

**

SECTION I

**

**Third Party**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this Web site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our Web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. To "opt-out," please click here. http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx. 

**Collection of Information**

Goldmic only collects personally identifiable information (such as name, email address, mailing address, telephone number) about You when You specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis. For example, We might ask for such information when We run a contest, when You register for subscription services, during product registration, in our online stores, and in connection with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat and bulletin boards), surveys, and voting and polling activities. 

You should be very cautious when You voluntarily disclose personal information (for example, name or email address) on bulletin boards, in chat areas, or the upload areas of our Site. That information, along with any other information You may disclose in your posting, can be collected, correlated, and used by third parties, and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Goldmic and are not subject to this Privacy Policy.

Goldmic also collects and archives transcripts of all of the Site's chat rooms. Such transcripts are used for market research and improvement of our Site and related products and services. In addition, Goldmic reserves the right to monitor the contents of all private messages sent by You on our Site for purposes of preventing abusive activity on the Site and improving our Site and related products and services. 

This website may utilize certain services provided by DoubleClick, Inc. (DoubleClick). For further information concerning DoubleClick's privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its services, please go to http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/

**Information Use**

Goldmic has a stringent Privacy Policy concerning how We use information about our members and the extent to which others may have access to this information. Member information is used for internal purposes only, such as market research, improvement of our marketing and promotional efforts, and improvement of our products, services and Site. We do not give, sell, rent, share or trade any identifiable personal information regarding our members to any third party, except as required by law or expressly permitted by a member. 

Goldmic may use your personally identifiable information to send You promotional and/or marketing information about related products, services and offerings from Us, unless You indicate You would like to "opt out" of receiving such materials. Goldmic reserves the right to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics, either internally or by sending this data to a third party for further analysis. We do this in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of our website and to create tailored marketing offerings. We may share this information with advertisers in aggregated, anonymous form. We may also use this aggregated, anonymous information to let advertisers know how many visitors have seen their banners and how many have clicked on them; advertisers will not be able to identify any individual from these analyses.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Goldmic may disclose personally identifiable information about You to a subsequent owner or operator of our Site or any of our services if We assign our rights and obligations regarding any of your information at the time of a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of our Site's assets and/or services to a subsequent owner or operator. You will be deemed to have consented to the disclosure to, and use by, a subsequent owner or operator of such Site or service, and your continued use of the Site or service signifies your agreement to be bound by the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of the Site's or service's subsequent owner or operator.

Goldmic may also disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in the following instances: 1) We have been given your consent to disclose; 2) We have previously informed You of the disclosure, including by means of our Privacy Policy; 3) We are required by law or court order to disclose, or We believe in good faith that the law requires it; 4) disclosure is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against, someone who may cause or be causing harm to, or interference with, our rights or property, other Site users, or anyone else; or 5) to respond to an inquiry, request or complaint that You have made. We may also use IP addresses in cooperation with Internet service providers to identify users if We deem it necessary to comply with laws, to enforce compliance with this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use, or to protect our Site, customers, or others.

**Cookies**

You should be aware that non-personally identifiable information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of Goldmic's web servers or through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files a website can use to recognize repeat users. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside of the website that he or she is visiting. Goldmic uses cookies to recognize visitors and more quickly provide personalized content or grant You unimpeded access to registered areas of our website. 

Information gathered through cookies also helps Us measure use of our Site. Cookie data allows Us to track usage behavior and compile data that We can use to improve the Site and target advertising. This data will generally be used in aggregate form; however, We may track specific users from time to time to help Us improve our products and services. Sometimes, advertisers or third parties hosting data for Goldmic will issue cookies. We cannot control the use of these cookies or the information that they gather.

You can easily turn off cookies in your browser. However, cookies are necessary to provide You with certain features available on our Site. Some areas of our Site, such as the login system, will not function properly without cookies. Enabling cookies ensures a smooth, efficient visit to our Site.

**IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever You access the Internet. All computer identification on the Internet is conducted with IP addresses, which allow computers and servers to recognize and communicate with each other. Upon visits to our Site, We will log your IP addresses, or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration, troubleshooting, record keeping, advertising reporting, improvement of our products and service and prevention of abusive activity on the Site. 

**Security**

We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that whatever information You provide Us will be maintained in a secure environment. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while We strive to protect your personal information, We cannot guarantee the security of any information You transmit to Us or from our products or services, and You provide such information at your own risk. Once We receive your transmission, We make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted We use industry standard SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. You, the member, are responsible for securing your password. We will never ask You for your password. We recommend that You sign out of your account completely and close your browser each time You visit the Site. This precaution is to prevent unauthorized access to your accounts by someone else who uses your computer or has access to same (e.g., public computers like Internet cafes or public libraries).

**Opting Out**

Upon request, We will allow You to opt out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of Goldmic, unless otherwise required by law, court order, or other government or law enforcement authority. Also, upon request, We will allow You to opt out of receiving email about the Site and related products and services, besides important Site announcements. You can make a request to opt out at any time by going to your account preferences web page. Additionally, should You choose to deactivate your account You can do so at any time by also going to your account preferences web page.

**Notification of Changes**

Goldmic reserves the right to change this policy at any time. In case of any material change, We will replace the "Privacy Policy" link on the home page of our Site with a link entitled "Updated Privacy Policy." All changes to the Privacy Policy will be effective when posted, and your continued use of the Site and related products and services after the posting will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

**Children's Privacy**

We recognize the sensitivity of personally identifiable information concerning children under the age of 13. We are committed to complying with all applicable laws and regulations regarding children, including the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 and will not knowingly collect, maintain, or disclose such information. If You are under 13, You should not enter any personally identifiable information about yourself on our Site or in any of our products. If You are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child under the age of 13 has submitted his or her personally identifiable information without your permission or consent, We will make reasonable efforts to remove the information from our database, at your request. To request the removal of your child's information, please email Us at  and be sure to include in your message the same username and/or email address and password that your child submitted. 

**Extent of Policy**

This Privacy Policy does not extend to the information volantarily provided by You to authorized third parties who are affiliates of Goldmic. Members are encouraged to read the Privacy Policy of our authorized third parties before providing any personal information. We may from time to time offer links to other websites from the our Site. Other websites may also reference, advertise, or link to our Site. We do not endorse or sponsor other websites, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, expressly disclaim any statements or assertions made on such websites, and deny all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other websites. You may arrive at one of these websites through clicking on an advertisement, as part of a co-branding arrangement, or simply by clicking a link on our Site. These websites might issue their own cookies or collect data or personally identifiable information. Use caution when visiting an external site.
